A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Penitentiary, 1796-1991 (bulk 1906-1970)
Library of Virginia
- Series IV. Office of the Superintendent, 1869-1991 (bulk 1908-1970)., Extent: 76.60 cubic feet of records and 19 volumes. (Box 391-572, 693 and Oversize Box 2., Volume 143-161.)
  - Series IV. Subseries E. Reports and Publications, 1921-1982 (bulk 1941-1982). (Box 558-566.)
    - Annual Reports, 1951-1952. (Box 558, Folder 2)
    - Annual Reports, 1952-1953. (Box 558, Folder 2)
    - Annual Reports, 1953-1954. (Box 558, Folder 3)
    - Annual Reports, 1954-1955. (Box 558, Folder 4)
    - Annual Reports, 1955-1956. (Box 558, Folder 5)
    - Annual Reports, 1956-1957. (Box 559, Folder 1)
    - Annual Reports, 1956-1957. (Box 559, Folder 2)
    - Annual Reports, 1957-1958. (Box 559, Folder 3)
    - Annual Reports, 1958-1959. (Box 559, Folder 4)
    - Annual Reports, 1959-1960. (Box 559, Folder 5)
    - Annual Reports, 1960-1961. (Box 559, Folder 6)
    - Annual Reports, 1961-1962. (Box 560, Folder 1)
    - Annual Reports, 1962-1963. (Box 560, Folder 2)
    - Annual Reports, 1963-1964. (Box 560, Folder 2)
    - Annual Reports, 1964-1965. (Box 560, Folder 3)
    - Annual Reports, 1965-1966. (Box 560, Folder 4)
    - Annual Reports, 1966-1967. (Box 560, Folder 5)
    - Annual Reports, 1967-1968. (Box 560, Folder 6)
    - Budget Material, 1951-1966. (Box 561, Folder 1)
    - Budget Material, 1951-1966. (Box 561, Folder 2)
    - Budget Material, 1951-1966. (Box 561, Folder 3)
    - List of Prisoners Convicted of Rape (prepared for Martinsville Seven Executions), 1907-1950. (Box 561, Folder 4)
    - Gas Reports, 1955-1959. (Box 561, Folder 5)
    - Gas Reports, 1955-1959. (Box 561, Folder 6)
    - Heating Plant Summary, August 1963-June 1966. (Box 562, Folder 1)
    - Hospital Material, 1952-1966. (Box 562, Folder 2)
    - Hospital Material, 1952-1966. (Box 562, Folder 3)
    - Hospital Material, 1952-1966. (Box 562, Folder 4)
    - Hospital Material, 1952-1966. (Box 562, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous Publications and Reports, 1934, 1939, 1950, 1954 and undated. (Box 562, Folder 6)
    - Monthly Punishment Reports, 1965-1967. (Box 562, Folder 7)
    - Population Reports, July 1941 to December 1944. (Volume 148)
    - Population Reports, January 1949 to December 1953. (Volume 149)
    - Annual Report of the Department of Corrections, 1943, 1978, 1979, 1980, 1981, 1982 (volumes) (Box 563)
    - Annual Report of the Department of Welfare and Institutions, 1962-1963 and 1965-1966 (volumes) (Box 563)
    - "A History of Organized Religious Work in Virginia's State Institutions", thesis by George F. Ricketts, August 1959. (Box 563, Folder 1)
    - The Prison Problem in Virginia, A Survey by the Prison Industries Reorganization Administration, 1939. (Box 563, Folder 1)
    - "A Brief History of the Virginia State Penitentiary" by James M. Good, December 1973 (2 copies). (Box 563, Folder 1)
    - Third Annual Report of the President and Superintendent of the Virginia Manual Labor School, 1903. (Box 563, Folder 2)
    - Virginia Manual Labor School for Boys, Twelfth Biennial Report to the General Assembly, 1921-1923 (2 copies). (Box 563, Folder 2)
    - Memorial Home for Girls, formerly Female Humane Society, 1805-1938. (Box 563, Folder 2)
    - Report of the Committee on the Study of the State Training Schools for Juvenile Delinquents, 24 July 1947. (Box 563, Folder 2)
    - Children and Youth in Trouble in Virginia: A Report by the Virginia State Crime Commission, December 1977 (volume). (Box 563)
    - Report, Dept. of Corrections, Capital Outlay Planning Unit, November 1980 (volume). (Box 563)
    - Step by Step: A Guide Through the Juvenile Justice System in Virginia, 1980 (volume). (Box 563)
    - A Study of the Program Components of the Virginia Juvenile Justice System, 1980 (volume). (Box 563)
    - Characteristics of Children Committed to the Virginia Department of Corrections, Fiscal Year 1982 (volume). (Box 564)
    - Virginia State Crime Commission, Report of the Organized Crime Detection Task Force, December 1971 (volume). (Box 564)
    - Report of the Virginia State Crime Commission to the Governor and the General Assembly of Virginia, January 1973 (volume). (Box 564)
    - Virginia State Crime Commission, First Report on Corrections, December 1973 (volume). (Box 564)
    - Report of Advisory Task Force to Study Local Jails for Virginia State Crime Commission, 15 December 1973 (volume). (Box 564)
    - Annual Report of the Virginia State Crime Commission, 1982 (volume). (Box 564)
    - Inmate Population Flow in the Virginia Correctional System, April 1977 (volume). (Box 564)
    - Fact Sheets on Institutions and Directions to Institutions, ca. 1981 (volume). (Box 564)
    - Adult Probation and Parole in Virginia, 1965 (volume). (Box 564)
    - The Criminal Justice System in Virginia: An Introduction for Planners, October 1974. (Box 564, Folder 1)
    - Proposed Capital Outlay and Community-Based Alternative Programs to Meet Virginia's Projected Felon Population, 1 September 1976. (Box 564, Folder 1)
    - Virginia Correctional Center for Women, Staff Manual, 1 September 1976 (volume). (Box 564)
    - House of Delegates Appropriations Committee Staff Report on Local Jails and the Department of Corrections, 12 July 1976 (volume). (Box 564)
    - An Insight to Corrections, 1975-1976 (volume). (Box 564)
    - Executive Summary of Goals for Virginia's Criminal Justice System (Final Report, Task Force on Criminal Justice Goals and Objectives), March 1977 (volume). (Box 564)
    - Corrections Options for the Eighties, Executive Summary, 1978 (2 copies) (volume). (Box 564)
    - Corrections Options for the Eighties (Full Report), 1978 (2 copies) (volume). (Box 564)
    - Statewide Symposium on Adult Community Corrections, 24-25 March 1981 (volume). (Box 564)
    - Guidelines for the Administration of Community Diversion Projects, November 1980 (volume). (Box 565)
    - Training Schedule, Virginia Department of Corrections Academy for Staff Development, 1982 (volume). (Box 565)
    - Maximum Security Treatment Center, Mecklenburg County, Virginia, undated (volume). (Box 565)
    - Manual of Standards for Outreach Detention Programs, undated (volume). (Box 565)
    - Children and Youth in Trouble in Virginia, Phase II, A Report by the Virginia State Crime Commission, May 1979 (volume). (Box 565)
    - Services in the Seventies to Virginia's Delinquent Children and Their Families, undated (volume). (Box 565)
    - Report of Bland Correctional Farm and 13 Field Units in Virginia Compiled by the Virginia State Crime Commission, 1974. (Box 565, Folder 1)
    - Virginia Department of Corrections, Population Summary, May 1982. (Box 565, Folder 1)
    - Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Rules and Regulations to Assure the Protection of the Subjects of Human Research, March 1981. (Box 565, Folder 1)
    - Virginia Community Diversion Incentive Act, 12 August 1980. (Box 565)
    - The Virginia Parole System: An Appraisal of its First Twelve Years, A Report Prepared for the Virginia Parole Board, 12 May 1955. (Box 565)
    - Adult Institutions Survey, 1982. (Box 565, Folder 2)
    - Correctional Officer Training in Virginia: A Final Report, August 1977. (Box 565)
    - Telephone Directory of the Virginia State Penitentiary, 1934. (Box 566, Folder 1)
    - Reflections of a Prison Warden, by Rice M. Youell, 3 October 1938. (Box 566, Folder 1)
    - Banquet Program, 27 June 1947. (Box 566, Folder 1)
    - Virginia State Penitentiary, Petition of Inmates, 9-27-1979 and Response, 11-5-1979 (volume). (Box 566)
    - "The Beacon", January-December 1939 (monthly inmate publication). (Box 566)
  - Series IV. Subseries F. Guard Logs, Virginia Penitentiary, 1972-1980. (Volumes 150-161.)
    This subseries contains 12 volumes. This subseries contains a variety of Virginia Penitentiary log books. The [Visitor's Sign-In] Day Book lists the date, time and signature of visitor. The [Prisoner] Package Receipt Book lists the date, prisoner's name, number and signature. The Night Log Books are arranged by date and shift and include notations of security checks (gates, fence, windows and bars) and reports of conduct violations, medical problems, transfer of inmates from various cells and receipt of new inmates. The Jail Log Books contain similar information.
    - [Visitor's Sign-In] Day Book, 16 December 1979 to 17 May 1980. (Volume 150)
    - [Prisoner] Package Receipt Book, 1 July 1976 to 13 January 1979. (Volume 151)
    - Night Log Book, 12 December 1974 to 7 March 1976. (Volume 152)
    - Night Log Book, 8 March 1976 to 16 February 1977. (Volume 153)
    - Night Log Book, 16 February 1977 to 1 January 1978. (Volume 154)
    - Night Log Book, 1 January 1978 to 23 December 1978. (Volume 155)
    - Jail Log Book, 26 April 1973 to 9 April 1974. (Volume 156)
    - Jail Log Book, 9 April 1974 to 1 January 1975. (Volume 157)
    - Jail Log Book, 28 July 1975 to 27 February 1976. (Volume 158)
    - Jail Log Book, 27 February 1976 to 5 September 1976. (Volume 159)
    - Weekend Duty Log Book, 18 February 1974 to 15 April 1978. (Volume 160)
    - Day Log Book for Dog Trainer, 11 April 1972 to 27 July 1978. (Volume 161)
  - Series IV. Subseries G: Reference Books, 1869-1931. (Box 567 and 693.)
    This subseries is housed in two boxes and contains published volumes of Acts of Assembly related to the Virginia Penitentiary, Report of the Secretary of the Commonwealth, and annual reports from other states.
    - Acts of Assembly, 1869-1870 (2 copies), 1870-1871 and 1872-1873 (volumes). (Box 567)
    - House Journal and Documents, 1876-1877 (volume). (Box 567)
    - Code of Virginia, 1888 (volume). (Box 567)
    - A Compilation of Laws Relating to the Virginia Penitentiary, 20 December 1904 (5 copies) (volume). (Box 567)
    - Report of the Secretary of the Commonwealth, 1908, 1918, 1928-29, 1930-1931 (volumes). (Box 567)
    - Virginia: A Handbook, 1893 (volume). (Box 567)
    - Virginia Penitentiary Laws, 1897 (volume). (Box 567)
    - A Compilation of Laws Relating to the Virginia Penitentiary, 20 December 1904 (volume). (Box 567)
    - An Act to Establish a Highway Commission together with an Act Creating the State Convict Road Force, July 1906 (volume). (Box 567)
    - Annual Reports from other States, 1882-1885, 1892-1903 (volumes). (Box 693)
  - Series IV. Subseries H: Photographs, 1976-1989 (bulk 1976-1979). (Box 568-572.)
    This subseries is housed in five boxes. This subseries contains photographs of guards, staff and staff events from the late 1970s. Many of the photographs are unidentified.
    - Staff Photographs, 1976-1989 (bulk 1976-1979).
      - May 1976-February 1977. (Box 568)
      - March 1977-July 1979. (Box 569)
      - August 1979-1989, undated and unidentified. (Box 570)
      - Unidentified Staff Events, 1979, 1981, 1986 and undated. (Box 571)
    - Unidentified Photographs
      - undated. (Box 572)
- Series V. State Convict Road Force, 1904-1965 (bulk 1906-1949)., Extent: 31.78 cubic feet of records and 50 volumes. (Box 573-659., Volume 162-203, 222, 255, 268-269, 272-274 and 287.)
  The State Convict Road Force series contains 50 volumes and is housed in 87 boxes. It is arranged into four (4) subseries. Subseries have been designated for: A. Prisoner Records; B. Diaries; C. Correspondence; and D. Financial Records. These records include diaries, correspondence, subject files, registers, rosters, index cards, reports, lists and financial records, This series documents the activities of the State Convict Road Force.
  Researchers should be aware that there are significant gaps within this series. For example there are very few correspondence prior to 1926 or prisoner registers after 1925. Topics include convict labor, State Convict Road Force operations (camp supplies, payrolls, camp inventories, rations for prisoners and camp bills), prisoner escapes, and punishment reports. Prisoners in this series are sometimes referred to as "jailmen" or "stripemen". Jailmen are prisoners convicted of a misdemeanor and sentenced to a short term (a year or less) on the State Convict Road Force. Stripemen are convicted felons sentenced to the road force. Unlike stripemen, jailmen are not included in the Prisoner Registers or Photographs found in Series II. Prisoner Records. Researchers should also note that additional State Convict Road Force records can be found in Series IV. Office of the Superintendent, Subseries C. State Convict Road Force.
  - Series V. Subseries A: Prisoner Records, 1904-1965 (bulk 1910-1949). (Box 573-620., Volume 162-187.)
    This subseries contains 26 volumes and 48 boxes. The Prisoner Records subseries is further divided into: A.I. Registers, 1908-1940; A.II. Rosters, 1904-1925; A.III. Jailor's Reports, 1907-1911, 1920, 1927-1928; A.IV. Index Cards, 1917-1965 (bulk 1919-1949); A.V. Prisoner Status Sheets, 1928-1929, 1936-1937; A.VI. Escape and Recapture Reports, 1911-1912, 1915-1916, 1932, 1934-1936, 1941; A.VII. Punishment Reports, 1910-1918, 1938; A.VIII. Statement of Prisoners, 1916-1918; and A.IX. Death Reports, 1911-1912.
    - Series V.A.I. Registers, 1908-1940. (Box 573., Volume 162-173.)
      There are 12 volumes and one box of Registers. The Monthly Reports volume contains statistical information by camp (costs to run the camp, number of convicts and jailmen) and lists of escaped, recaptured and deaths of prisoners. The four Jailmen Registers are arranged chronologically and include: name, race, camp assigned, place of conviction, law violated, date received, sentence, date of discharge and detailed physical description. There are three unidentified index volumes for Jail Prisoners. The Discharge Lists (2 volumes and one box) contain the name of prisoner, race, where sentenced, when received and date term expires.
      - Monthly Reports, October 1909 to August 1912. (Volume 162)
      - Discharge Register for State Convict Road Force (by Camp -includes Catawba, Lime Plant No. 2 and Quarry), 1909-1919. (Volume 163)
      - Jail Men Register, 10 August 1906 to 28 September 1912. (Volume 164)
      - Jail Men Register, 20 October 1912 to 8 March 1915. (Volume 165)
      - Jail Men Register, 1 March 1915 to 28 October 1916. (Volume 166)
      - Jail Men Register, 27 October 1916 to 29 January 1918. (Volume 167)
      - [Unidentified] Index, Convict Road Force, Jail Prisoners, undated. (Volume 168)
      - [Unidentified] Index, Convict Road Force, Jail Prisoners, undated. (Volume 169)
      - [Unidentified] Index, Convict Road Force, Stripe Men, undated. (Volume 170)
      - Escapes at Large, ca. 1908-1915. (Volume 171)
      - Jail Men Discharge Lists, March 1910 to May 1920. (Volume 172)
      - Jail Men Discharge Lists, May 1920 to September 1935 (appears to be stripe men only - most pages are blank) (Volume 173)
      - State Convict Road Force, Monthly Discharge Lists, 1909-1910. (Box 573, Folder 1)
      - State Convict Road Force, Monthly Discharge Lists, February and March 1918. (Box 573, Folder 2)
      - State Convict Road Force, Monthly Discharge Lists, November 1918. (Box 573, Folder 3)
      - State Convict Road Force, Monthly Discharge Lists, March, September and October 1920. (Box 573, Folder 4)
      - State Convict Road Force, Monthly Discharge Lists, December 1933 to March 1934. (Box 573, Folder 5)
      - State Convict Road Force, Monthly Discharge Lists, April 1938 to July 1938. (Box 573, Folder 6)
      - State Convict Road Force, Monthly Discharge Lists, January 1939 to February 1940 (not inclusive). (Box 573, Folder 7)
    - Series V.A.II. Rosters, 1904-1925. (Volume 174-187.)
      There are 14 volumes of Rosters arranged by camp and by date received therein. Both jailmen and stripemen are included unless noted. Each volume contains the name of prisoner, race, place of conviction, law violated, date received, sentence, date of discharge and detailed physical description.
      - Record of Prisoners Assigned to County Road Forces (Stripe Men only), 1904 to 1913. (Volume 174)
      - Record of Prisoners Assigned to State Convict Road Force, September 1912 to April 1913. (Volume 175)
      - Record of Prisoners, Camp 6, ca. 1916 to ca. 1923. (Volume 176)
      - Record of Prisoners (Jail Men), Camp 26, 15 April 1913 to 16 October 1917. (Volume 177)
      - Record of Prisoners (Stripe Men), Camp 7, ca. November 1917 to 6 October 1923. (Volume 178)
      - Record of Prisoners, Camp 14, 30 September 1908 to 20 February 1920. (Volume 179)
      - Record of Prisoners, Camp 15, 21 November 1910 to ca. 1919. (Volume 180)
      - Record of Prisoners, Camp 16, 9 November 1910 to 10 January 1921. (Volume 181)
      - Record of Prisoners, Camp 17, 12 March 1912 to 12 October 1922. (Volume 182)
      - Record of Prisoners, Camp 22, ca. 1908 to 22 November 1917. (Volume 183)
      - Record of Prisoners, Camp 26, ca. December 1913 to 22 November 1923. (Volume 184)
      - Record of Prisoners, Camp 26 (Jail Men only), ca. 1917 to 4 November 1919. (Volume 185)
      - Record of Prisoners, Camp 28, ca. 1913 to ca. 1923. (Volume 186)
      - Record of Prisoners, Camp 30, ca. 1908 to 14 August 1924 (also contains ledger of supplies purchased, February 1924 to August 1925). (Volume 187)
    - Series V.A.III. Jailor's Reports, 1907-1911, 1920, 1927-1928. (Box 574-597.)
      The 24 boxes of Jailor's Reports are arranged chronologically (1907-1911) or by report number (1920, 1927-1928). These reports were created by county jailors and sent to the Virginia Penitentiary. Each report lists: locality, date, name of jailman, race, offense, date put in jail, sentence, time to serve, date of expiration of sentence, and remarks. Some reports include statements from a physician stating the prisoner is able to work on the Road Force.
      - Jailor's Reports, Camp 3, May 1911. (Box 574, Folder 1)
      - Jailor's Reports, Camp 3, April 1911. (Box 574, Folder 2)
      - Jailor's Reports, Camp 3, March 1911. (Box 574, Folder 3)
      - Jailor's Reports, Camp 3, February 1911. (Box 574, Folder 4)
      - Jailor's Reports, Camp 3, January 1911. (Box 574, Folder 5)
      - Jailor's Reports, Camp 3, December 1910. (Box 574, Folder 6)
      - Jailor's Reports, Camp 3, October 1910. (Box 574, Folder 7)
      - Jailor's Reports, Camp 3, September 1910. (Box 574, Folder 8)
      - Jailor's Reports, Camp 3, August 1910. (Box 574, Folder 9)
      - Jailor's Reports, Camp 3, July 1910. (Box 574, Folder 10)
      - Jailor's Reports, Camp 3, June 1910. (Box 574, Folder 11)
      - Jailor's Reports, Camp 3, May 1910. (Box 574, Folder 12)
      - Jailor's Reports, Camp 3, April 1910. (Box 575, Folder 1)
      - Jailor's Reports, Camp 3, March 1910. (Box 575, Folder 2)
      - Jailor's Reports, Camp 3, February 1910. (Box 575, Folder 3)
      - Jailor's Reports, Camp 3, January 1910. (Box 575, Folder 4)
      - Jailor's Reports, Camp 3, December 1909. (Box 575, Folder 5)
      - Jailor's Reports, Camp 3, November 1909. (Box 575, Folder 6)
      - Jailor's Reports, Camp 3, October 1909. (Box 575, Folder 7)
      - Jailor's Reports, Camp 3, September 1909. (Box 575, Folder 8)
      - Jailor's Reports, Camp 3, August 1909. (Box 575, Folder 9)
      - Jailor's Reports, Camp 3, July 1909. (Box 575, Folder 10)
      - Jailor's Reports, Camp 3, June 1909. (Box 575, Folder 11)
      - Jailor's Reports, Camp 3, May 1909. (Box 575, Folder 12)
      - Jailor's Reports, Camp 3, April 1909. (Box 575, Folder 13)
      - Jailor's Reports, Camp 3, March 1909. (Box 575, Folder 14)
      - Jailor's Reports, Camp 3, February 1909. (Box 575, Folder 15)
      - Jailor's Reports, Camp 3, January 1909. (Box 575, Folder 16)
      - Jailor's Reports, Camp 3, November 1908. (Box 576, Folder 1)
      - Jailor's Reports, Camp 3, September 1908. (Box 576, Folder 2)
      - Jailor's Reports, Camp 3, August 1908. (Box 576, Folder 3)
      - Jailor's Reports, Camp 3, July 1908. (Box 576, Folder 4)
      - Jailor's Reports, Camp 3, June 1908. (Box 576, Folder 5)
      - Jailor's Reports, Camp 3, May 1908. (Box 576, Folder 6)
      - Jailor's Reports, Camp 3, April 1908. (Box 576, Folder 7)
      - Jailor's Reports, Camp 3, March 1908. (Box 576, Folder 8)
      - Jailor's Reports, Camp 3, February 1908. (Box 576, Folder 9)
      - Jailor's Reports, Camp 3, December 1907. (Box 576, Folder 10)
      - Jailor's Reports, Camp 3, November 1907. (Box 576, Folder 11)
      - Jailor's Reports, Camp 3, October 1907. (Box 576, Folder 12)
      - Jailor's Reports, Camp 3, September 1907. (Box 576, Folder 13)
      - Jailor's Reports, Camp 3, August 1907. (Box 576, Folder 14)
      - No. 1003 - Camp 22, 22 March 1920. (Box 577, Folder 1)
      - No. 1004 - Camp 6, 22 March 1920. (Box 577, Folder 1)
      - No. 1005 - Camp 26, 22 March 1920. (Box 577, Folder 1)
      - No. 5100 - Camp 12, Petersburg, 14 April 1927. (Box 577, Folder 2)
      - No. 5101 - Camp 22, Appomattox County, 9 April 1927. (Box 577, Folder 3)
      - No. 5102 - Camp 3, Norfolk, 13 April 1927. (Box 577, Folder 4)
      - No. 5103 - Camp 21, Fauquier County, 7 April 1927. (Box 577, Folder 5)
      - No. 5104 - Camp 1, Smyth County, 13 April 1927. (Box 577, Folder 6)
      - No. 5105 - Camp 22, Richmond, 15 April 1927. (Box 577, Folder 7)
      - No. 5106 - Camp 30, Albemarle County, 14 April 1927. (Box 577, Folder 8)
      - No. 5107 - Camp 30, Charlottesville, 7 April 1927. (Box 577, Folder 9)
      - No. 5108 - Camp 30, Charles City County, 7 April 1927. (Box 577, Folder 10)
      - No. 5109 - Camp 18, Spotsylvania County, April 1927. (Box 577, Folder 11)
      - No. 5110 - Camp 24, Roanoke, 15 April 1927. (Box 577, Folder 12)
      - No. 5111 - Camp 4, Amherst County, 11 April 1927. (Box 577, Folder 13)
      - No. 5112 - Camp 5, Wise County, 14 April 1927. (Box 577, Folder 14)
      - No. 5113 - Camp 3, Norfolk, 13 April 1927. (Box 577, Folder 15)
      - No. 5114 - Camp 29, Frederick County, 8 April 1927. (Box 577, Folder 16)
      - No. 5115 - Camp 22, Lynchburg, 11 April 1927. (Box 577, Folder 17)
      - No. 5116 - Camp 12, Greensville County, 7 April 1927. (Box 577, Folder 18)
      - No. 5117 - Camp 32, Bath County, 11 April 1927. (Box 577, Folder 19)
      - No. 5118 - Camp 9, Rockbridge County, 15 April 1927. (Box 577, Folder 20)
      - No. 5119 - Camp 21, Fauquier County, 7 April 1927. (Box 577, Folder 21)
      - No. 5120 - Camp 30, Albemarle County, 14 April 1927. (Box 577, Folder 22)
      - No. 5121 - Camp 12, Greensville County, 7 April 1927. (Box 578, Folder 1)
      - No. 5122 - Camp 22, Mathews County, 9 April 1927. (Box 578, Folder 2)
      - No. 5123 - Camp 10, Clarke County, 13 April 1927. (Box 578, Folder 3)
      - No. 5124 - Camp 12, Halifax County, 11 April 1927. (Box 578, Folder 4)
      - No. 5125 - Camp 8, Amherst County, April 1927. (Box 578, Folder 5)
      - No. 5126 - Camp 3, Norfolk City, 11 April 1927. (Box 578, Folder 6)
      - No. 5127 - Camp 7, Caroline County, 25 April 1927. (Box 578, Folder 7)
      - No. 5128 - Camp 10, Clarke County, 22 April 1927. (Box 578, Folder 8)
      - No. 5129 - Camp 3, Southampton County, 23 April 1927. (Box 578, Folder 9)
      - No. 5130 - Camp 9, Bath County, 19 April 1927. (Box 578, Folder 10)
      - No. 5131 - Camp 22, Lynchburg, 21 April 1927. (Box 578, Folder 11)
      - No. 5132 - Camp 1, Washington County, 23 April 1927. (Box 578, Folder 12)
      - No. 5134 - Camp 24, Roanoke, 23 April 1927. (Box 578, Folder 13)
      - No. 5135 - Camp 10, Clarke County, 22 April 1927. (Box 578, Folder 14)
      - No. 5136 - Camp 14, Bland County, 25 April 1927. (Box 578, Folder 15)
      - No. 5137 - Camp 10, Page County, 23 April 1927. (Box 578, Folder 16)
      - No. 5138 - Camp 32, Bath County, 20 April 1927. (Box 578, Folder 17)
      - No. 5139 - Camp 32, Bath County, 20 April 1927. (Box 578, Folder 18)